<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BizarrePower</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="image">asjfbajkf</string>
    <string name="itemheading"><![CDATA[Products & Services\n  UPS]]></string>>



    <string-array name="clientnames">
        1 temple<item>SreePisharikavu Temple  </item>
        2 gov<item>Koyilandy Muncipality  </item>
        3 hosp<item>Mental Hospital kuthiravattom </item>
        4 gov<item>FCI Kozhikode   </item>
        5 institu<item>KMCT Group of Instituition  </item>
        6 colg<item>NMSM GOVT Colege, Wayanad   </item>
        7 collge<item>Model ITI, Kozhikode </item>
        8 collge<item>Womens Polytechnic, Malapparamba GP   </item>
        9 college<item>Womens ITI, Malikkadavu   </item>
        10college<item>SARBTM GOVT College, Koyilandy </item>
        11govt<item>Perambra GP</item>
        12colg<item>CKG Memmorial GOVT College,Perambra</item>
        13collg<item>ITI Elathur</item>
        14govt<item>Meenangadi GP</item>




    </string-array>
    <string-array name="clientmessages">
       1 <item>\"Bizarre provided the best equipments in low cost without compromising the quality \"   </item>
        2<item>\"Everything is communicated in a professional and timely manner\"   </item>
        3<item>\"Bizarre is consistent in meeting our expectation\" </item>
        4<item>\"Total work was way too good\"</item>
        5<item>\"We have always received good service from Bizarre.\"</item>
        6<item>\"Excellent work all the way around\"</item>
        7<item>\"Service is extraordinary\"</item>
       8 <item>\"Time and quality have always met our expectation\"</item>
        9<item>\"Every products are of excellent standards\"</item>
        10<item>\"Excellent and efficient\"</item>
        11<item>\"Everything was done with in time limit\"</item>
        12<item>\"Good service\"</item>
        13<item>\"Supplied high quality products\"</item>
        14<item>\"Efficient company \"</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="firstdesc">
       \" The most prestigious and progressive vendor and a leader in the backup power provisioning
        industry focus on doing business of reliable and the “best in class” UPS, Inverter, Solar
        Products, Batteries, Computers and related accessories,
        Networking  to all power needs and provides end-to-end solutions.\"



    </string>
    <string name="desc2">




      <![CDATA[ \n \n o	                We are authorized distributors & dealers of UPS, Inverters, Solar Systems, Servo Stabilizers, Batteries and IT equipments. We Offer a wide range of power electronics products for all commercial and residential needs of users. We are mainly doing the business from  NUMERIC, IGA-TECH, HYKON, APC etc and HP, ACER, DELL, LENOVO etc; – well known branded products in this industry. We also focus on selling enhanced quality, reliable and performance based products having quality certificates like ISO.
\n \n \no	                   We take up the responsibility of providing after SALES & SERVICE for all kind of UPS, Inverters& Computers manufactured by others also. We are proud to announce our best service support that is well received and complemented by all of our customers. We have well-developed professional service setup with dedicated professionals for after sale service. We are focusing to delight customers by improving quality of life.
\n \n \n o	               We have achieved a tremendous growth primarily by gaining 100% customer satisfaction and trading the best products in quality and cost effectiveness to our customers. Our products and services play a key role in successful operations of various Industries including but not limited to major Govt & Central Govt Departments, Banks, Hospitals, Engg. Colleges, Schools, Large and Small Scale businesses.
Our Vision
To be recognized as the leading power solutions provider.]]>

    </string>
    <string name="vision">
        <![CDATA[\"To be recognized as the leading power solutions provider\"]]>
    </string>
    <string name="mission">
       \" We committed to providing the best quality products with competitive price and services exceeding our customers’ expectations in the most professional and ethical manner.\"

    </string>
    <string name="address">E3/33/6687, OPAL COMPLEX,Water Authority Road,
    Malapparamba, Kozhikode-673009</string>
    <string name="phonenum">+91 9400623700,     \n0495 2536304</string>
    <string name="email">bizarrepower@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="location">https://www.google.co.in/maps/place/Bizarre+Power+Solution/@11.2867352,75.8031745,15z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x0:0x46b44d1b2aa1c7b!8m2!3d11.2867352!4d75.8031745</string>
<string name="fb">https://www.facebook.com/bizarrepowersolutions/</string>
    <string name="programming"><![CDATA[Developed by:]]></string>


</resources>
